Sentence,Entities
"Google is a tech giant headquartered in Mountain View.","[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (39, 52, 'LOC')]"
"Apple released the iPhone 15 in September.","[(0, 5, 'ORG')]"
"Elon Musk founded SpaceX in 2002.","[(0, 9, 'PERSON'), (17, 23, 'ORG')]"
"Amazon has offices in Seattle and New York.","[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (21, 28, 'LOC'), (33, 41, 'LOC')]"
"Microsoft is based in Redmond, Washington.","[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (20, 27, 'LOC')]"
"Facebook changed its name to Meta.","[(0, 8, 'ORG')]"
"The Eiffel Tower is located in Paris, France.","[(4, 17, 'LOC'), (32, 37, 'LOC'), (39, 45, 'LOC')]"
"Bill Gates co-founded Microsoft.","[(0, 10, 'PERSON'), (23, 32, 'ORG')]"
"Jeff Bezos was the CEO of Amazon.","[(0, 10, 'PERSON'), (27, 33, 'ORG')]"
"Nike is known for its slogan 'Just Do It'.","[(0, 4, 'ORG')]"
"Tesla announced a new model in 2023.","[(0, 5, 'ORG')]"
"Google's parent company is Alphabet.","[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (25, 33, 'ORG')]"
"IBM has been a leader in technology for decades.","[(0, 3, 'ORG')]"
"Walt Disney founded the Disney Company in 1923.","[(0, 11, 'PERSON'), (23, 29, 'ORG')]"
"YouTube is a popular video-sharing platform.","[(0, 7, 'ORG')]"
"Intel is a major player in the semiconductor industry.","[(0, 5, 'ORG')]"
"Elon Musk is also the CEO of Tesla.","[(0, 9, 'PERSON'), (28, 33, 'ORG')]"
"Coca-Cola is a famous beverage company.","[(0, 9, 'ORG')]"
"Amazon acquired Whole Foods in 2017.","[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (17, 27, 'ORG')]"
"Netflix produces original content for streaming.","[(0, 7, 'ORG')]"
"Starbucks has its headquarters in Seattle.","[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (30, 37, 'LOC')]"
"Elon Musk's vision includes space travel.","[(0, 9, 'PERSON')]"
"Twitter is a social media platform.","[(0, 7, 'ORG')]"
"The Statue of Liberty is in New York.","[(4, 21, 'LOC'), (28, 36, 'LOC')]"
"Microsoft acquired LinkedIn in 2016.","[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (19, 27, 'ORG')]"
"Shakespeare wrote many famous plays.","[(0, 11, 'PERSON')]"
"Amazon Prime offers various streaming services.","[(0, 12, 'ORG')]"
"Bill Gates has been a prominent philanthropist.","[(0, 10, 'PERSON')]"
"The Great Wall of China is an ancient fortification.","[(4, 22, 'LOC'), (26, 31, 'LOC')]"
"IBM was founded over a century ago.","[(0, 3, 'ORG')]"
"Elon Musk's company, SpaceX, launched the Falcon Heavy.","[(0, 9, 'PERSON'), (18, 24, 'ORG'), (39, 50, 'PRODUCT')]"
"Facebook has billions of users worldwide.","[(0, 8, 'ORG')]"
"Toyota is known for its reliable cars.","[(0, 6, 'ORG')]"
"Google Maps provides navigation services.","[(0, 11, 'ORG')]"
"Warren Buffett is a famous investor.","[(0, 13, 'PERSON')]"
"Microsoft Office is a suite of productivity tools.","[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (10, 16, 'PRODUCT')]"
"Amazon Web Services offers cloud computing solutions.","[(0, 16, 'ORG')]"
"Sundar Pichai is the CEO of Google.","[(0, 13, 'PERSON'), (28, 34, 'ORG')]"
"Tesla's Gigafactory is located in Nevada.","[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (29, 35, 'LOC')]"
"Microsoft launched Windows 11 in 2021.","[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (19, 26, 'PRODUCT')]"
"Bill Gates stepped down from Microsoft's board.","[(0, 10, 'PERSON'), (29, 38, 'ORG')]"
"Jeff Bezos owns The Washington Post.","[(0, 10, 'PERSON'), (16, 36, 'ORG')]"
"The Mona Lisa is housed in the Louvre.","[(4, 13, 'LOC'), (31, 37, 'LOC')]"
"Uber is a ride-sharing company.","[(0, 4, 'ORG')]"
"Amazon Prime Day offers exclusive deals.","[(0, 12, 'ORG')]"
"Steve Jobs was a co-founder of Apple.","[(0, 10, 'PERSON'), (32, 37, 'ORG')]"
"Coca-Cola's headquarters are in Atlanta, Georgia.","[(0, 9, 'ORG'), (28, 35, 'LOC'), (37, 44, 'LOC')]"
"Bill Gates is one of the richest people in the world.","[(0, 10, 'PERSON')]"
"Tesla's new Roadster is incredibly fast.","[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (11, 19, 'PRODUCT')]"
"Mark Zuckerberg created Facebook while at Harvard.","[(0, 14, 'PERSON'), (24, 32, 'ORG'), (43, 50, 'LOC')]"
"Google's Chrome browser is widely used.","[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (8, 14, 'PRODUCT')]"
"Amazon's AWS is a leader in cloud services.","[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (8, 11, 'ORG')]"
"Steve Wozniak co-founded Apple.","[(0, 12, 'PERSON'), (24, 29, 'ORG')]"
"The Colosseum is a historic landmark in Rome.","[(4, 14, 'LOC'), (39, 43, 'LOC')]"
"The Googleplex is located in Mountain View.","[(4, 15, 'LOC'), (31, 44, 'LOC')]"
"Amazon Kindle is a popular e-reader.","[(0, 6, 'ORG'), (7, 13, 'PRODUCT')]"
"Siri is Apple's voice-activated assistant.","[(0, 4, 'ORG'), (8, 13, 'ORG')]"
"Disneyland is located in Anaheim, California.","[(0, 10, 'LOC'), (22, 29, 'LOC'), (31, 41, 'LOC')]"
"Tim Cook is the CEO of Apple.","[(0, 8, 'PERSON'), (24, 29, 'ORG')]"
"Amazon's Alexa is a virtual assistant.","[(0, 6, 'ORG')]"
